

LUCAS VIANA

ROPE ACCESS TECHNICIAN

8

PROFILE

Passionate about working at height, always willing to delivery the best result with safety and responsible with the team. Always open to learning from new experiences and new co-workes, I always make myself available with humility and desire to grow.

WORK EXPERIENCE

Factor Corda

Rope Access Technician

2024 - PRESENT

- Perform repairs and paintings vertically using the middle of the strings as access. Always staying the security and the fulfillment of the goals.
 Washing of facades, cleaning of gutters, safety inspections and
- installantion of falling pipes. Waterproofing and cleaning of open and confinado spaces.

•

2024 - 2024

Milet Alpinismo

Rope Access Technician and Painter

 Painting work, repair and maintenance of buildings of high height and difficult access. Always using advanced security methods to complete

Alpincentro Lda

2022 - 2024

Rope Access Technician

- Responsible for several height works, in the area of construction and maintenance making use of rope access.
- In charge of the safety of the work team, always focused on safe and dynamic conclusions.

P

EDUCATION

Institute Northwest of Birigui

2014 - 2017

Secondary Education

OnRope Training

2024

Irata Level 1 Gwo Bst

CONTACT

- +351 913 873 669
- ✓ lukx.max@gmail.com
- Street of church, 26A, Portugal

SKILLS

- Focus
- Persistence
- Teamwork
- Leadership
- Effective Communication

LANGUAGES

- English (A2)
- Spanish (Basic)

MORE

Driving Licence A/B A1

Authorized Work Permit